In the window of 2D, right-click and choose to add a background image.
Add the attached version to the background image.
Select the multidirectional tool, click along the background image to draw the outline.
Press Ctrl and click to draw the curve point.
Release Ctrl and click to re-create the curve point.
Click the starting point again to complete the creation of the outline.
Then select the front and sleeve versions and press Ctrl D to create a symmetrical version.
Use the edit version tool to select the middle version and the back middle line.
Then select the symmetry function in the menu in the right-click.
Open the arrangement point and arrange the version on the map arrangement point.
The sleeve version needs to be arranged on the outside of the arm.
Since the back is a complete version, please place it on the back arrangement point.
Press Ctrl and click to re-create the curve point.
The back and sleeve versions do not need to be simulated at the moment.
Use the position tool to move the front right to the left front side to prevent collision.
Use the sewing tool to sew the outside of the version together.
Please confirm that the sewing line length is correct.
Select the M-B-N free sewing line in the sewing line menu to create a sewing line between multiple sewing lines.
The method of using the tool is similar to free sewing.
Click once from the right side of the sleeve in the order in the video.
Finally, click the starting point again to complete the selection of the first set of lines.
Press Enter to confirm that the first set of lines has been selected and completed.
Then repeat the action to complete the second set of lines.
After opening the simulation, you can see that the sewing line on the sleeve is located on the right side.
In this way, the sewing line on the side is hidden in the elbow position.
Create an inner line to fold the collar.
The fold angle will be increased to more than 180 degrees.
The panel will fold inward along the inner line position.
The printed front panel will help the collar fold neatly.
Press W to click on the costume.
The costume can be created with a fixed needle.
You can adjust the arrangement position by moving the fixed needle.
Select the button to create a button and click on the corresponding position on the panel.
Use the option to move the button to copy and paste the button.
When pasting, press the right button to enter the specific number.
Click on the button inside to refer to the wrong button image.
Please check your
distance points to figure out which button is correct.
After you done theatering.
Press H to crack open your Aub sectors.
After you finished the南 sleeveال
press H and press H and hold down .
At this moment,
Activate the collar and sew it to the collar seat
Then select to add to the outside to arrange the plate
If the collar is not stable, you can harden the plate
Make its attribute hardening faster and more stable
After stabilizing, remove hardening
Use a free sewing tool to sew the collar and the collar seat together
Make the leather slide-down lambskin fabric
Drag it to the fabric used to change the fabric
Choose a color in the color palette or select a color with the color dispenser
In the Hardware and Trims folder, you can load the shoulder pad or other accessories to the work area
Use the positioning ball tool to move the shoulder pad to the shoulder area
The冷冻电肩版片已将它们定格在3D空间中将它们的层级设置为负数,以便加客穿着到电肩外部
Hide the cover for easy confirmation that the shoulder pad is good enough for the body
Active simulation will arise a shoulder matter for the shoulder of the shoulder pad
Choose the inner part of the supervising layer to create the Trevor estate
Choose the inner part to prevent the interface with the trans aumento of the newly created version from cl Parkinson's
不 bij
Remove the joints of the baseboard pieces, and set the baseboard pieces of the baseboard pieces as symmetrical pieces.
Add a fixing needle to the corner of the collar.
Select the panels on the outer layer and modify the shrink rate to 101% to create a fold on the outer layer through the difference in size.
Reduce the particle diameter to 8 to get more detail folds.
Add a elastic band to get a more realistic embroidered panel effect.
Measure the total length of the
elastic band, and then create a rectangular panel based on the length.
The height of the rectangular panel is 10 mm.
Create a symmetrical elastic band panel and sew it to the panel.
The length of the elastic band is 10 mm.
Sometimes when you use the add to side tool, the panel will move to the wrong side.
Re-activate the sleeve panel and hide them.
Check if the elastic band panel is only attached to the sleeve side.
If not, please click the add to side function again.
You can hide the elastic band panel.
The sleeve panel is now back on the sleeve side.
When the elastic band is in the correct position, sew the side line together.
Increase the conflict thickness of the elastic band, so it will be elastic along the seam line.
Apply a new fabric type to the elastic band.
and change the physical properties of the fabric to Trim for Green Leather.
The fabric has a very high bending strength,
using this fabric can make the elastic band become completely without wrinkles, very hard.
Due to the anti-activation of the sleeve version,
the elastic band may have a small part and the sleeve insertion.
The cold outer layer version sets the layer of the sleeve version as 1.
The straps are set to the 5.6 mm and the height is 0.6 mm,
which is about 1.5 cm.
The sleeve might be more loose and also the seam allowance will be adjusted,
so the sleeve will not be loose and a little bit loose.
Then activate the simulation,
the elastic band is simulated to be close to the sleeve version.
When all versions are stable,
the layer setting is 0.
Activate the simulation,
the elastic band will lift up the sleeve,
and the seam allowances will be more obvious.
Thank you.